# Hossein Azami

Istanbul, Turkey



hossein.azami@gmail.com



+905526278675



linkedin.com/in/hossein-azami-7b90a3189

### **Summary**

Experienced web developer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in Software Project Management, Software Design, C# Programming, Micro Services, Domain Driven Design (DDD), CQRS, .net Core, ASP.NET Core, REST full API, ASP.NET MVC, Blazor and SignalR. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Computer from Meybod Azad University.

#### **Experience**



#### 🎇 Senior Project Manager

Global Testing

Oct 2020 - Present (1 year 11 months +)

- Global Candidate (https://globalcandidate.com)
- Bilnet Schools System (https://bilnetdigital.com/)
- Global Testing (https://globaltesting.com)
- Qkids Store (https://qkidsstore.com)

## 🎿 Senior Project Manager

Respina Radyn IT Co.

Sep 2010 - Dec 2019 (9 years 4 months)

### Web Developer

Tehran Municipality ICT Organization

Feb 2008 - Mar 2011 (3 years 2 months)

- Developing Project Manager Software as developer
- Developing Contract Management System as project manager
- Developing Urban system as developer

### Software Architect

Gostaresh Informatic Iranian

Jun 2005 - Mar 2007 (1 year 10 months)

Developing online Insurance System

## 📂 Application Developer

شرکت مهندسی مشاور تدوین فرآیند .Tadvin Farayand Co

Feb 2005 - May 2005 (4 months)

Purchasing system and purchasing tracking from Tadvin financial and administrative systems set - as programmer

### Web Developer

Pishgaman Isatis Mar 2004 - Oct 2004 (8 months) Parnian Madrese Smart School Project in Yazd - as programmer

### **Education**



#### Meybod Azad University

Bachelor's degree, Computer Hardware Engineering 2001 - 2005

#### **Licenses & Certifications**



Sololearn

1080-17810338

#### **Skills**

Microsoft SQL Server • tfs • Transact-SQL (T-SQL) • DotNetNuke (DNN) • Project Management • Domain-Driven Design (DDD) • REST APIs • Software Development • Analytical Skills • Software **Project Management**